Preliminary Guide to the Lou Chibbaro Washington Blade senior reporter files (Washington Blade donation), 1980-2001 MS2245
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Gay Delegates, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- DC Gay Delegates (updated), undated (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Gay doctors group meets with Shalala, 1996 February 16 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Gay elected officials conference, Chapel Hill, NC, 1992 November 20-22 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Gay ex-Marine incident, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Gay Federal Workers "come out" newspaper ad, 1993 October 04 (Box 69, Folder 12)
- Gay Footballers, undated (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Gay games/stonewall calendar, undated (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Gay Health Care providers, undated (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Gay helpline, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Gay Hindus, undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Gay hispanic group enlace link, undated (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Gay immigration, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Gay Irish, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Gay issues, newspaper articles, 1998-2000 (Box 65, Folder 4)
- Gay Latinos, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Gay and lesbian resources, 1991-1992 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Gay and Lesbian Services Guide, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Gay and Lesbian Veterans of America (Dane Hays), undated (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Gay man stabbed outside Badlands, 1995 August 26 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Gay man sues DC Army-Navy club, 1996 June 04 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Gay men and lesbians opposing violence GLOV, undated (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Gay military intelligence officer expose, undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Gay Money, undated (Box 54, Folder 21)
- Gay Murders, undated (Box 54, Folder 22)
- Gay Murders, undated (Box 65, Folder 7)
- Gay porn prosecution update, 1992 June (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Gay porn star murdered in LA, undated (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Gay Pride block party ousts band, 1995 June 17 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Gay Radio, undated (Box 68, Folder 4)
- Gay rights issues, undated (Box 67, Folder 4)
- Gay Rights press packet, undated (Box 67, Folder 2)
- Gay Rights press packet, undated (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Gay runners, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Gay Teen TV, undated (Box 60, Folder 9)
- Gay veterans meet Pentagon official, 1997 May 05 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Gay Violence, undated (Box 54, Folder 24)
- Gay volleyballers, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Gay, Social Security Administration employee wins harassment complaint, 1995 September (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Gay.com, undated (Box 65, Folder 10)
- Gay.Net, undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Gay-contra connection, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Gays arrested in Cuba, undated (Box 47, Folder 14)
- Gays in DC Fall of '69; gay history, undated (Box 69, Folder 14)
- Gays organize Rodney King demo in DC, undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Gays speak at King Day March in Atlanta, 1997 January 20 (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Gays to run for shadow House seat, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Gays want out of military, undated (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Gays/KGB - future story (Jane Hunter), undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Genetics and homosexuality, undated (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Georgetown Group House proposal, undated (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Georgetown, undated (Box 58, Folder 2)
- Gertrude Stein Democratic Club, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- GLAA ratings - DC council races, undated (Box 42, Folder 18)
- GLAA ratings, 1992 September (Box 20, Folder 1)
- GLAA ratings Ward 6 elec., 1997 (Box 66, Folder 17)
- GLAA, undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
  Meeting notes from reporter who attended many meetings
- GLAA, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  Meeting notes from reporter who attended many meetings.
- GLAA, 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- GLAAD, undated (Box 60, Folder 4)
- GLAAD and Laura Schlessinger, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 9)
- GLAAD, 1996 August (Box 42, Folder 19)
- Glen Turner obit, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Gleo, undated (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Globe, undated (Box 54, Folder 23)
- GLOV, undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
- GLSEN, undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
- GNN, undated (Box 68, Folder 6)
- GOP loses bid for VA, 1995 November 10 (Box 53, Folder 15)
- Gore Meets Gay Leaders at White House, 1997 January 17 (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Gore Meets with Pharmaceutical Firms, 1996 February 10 (Box 57, Folder 12)
- Greaseman, undated (Box 60, Folder 7)
- Group warfare, undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Gunder write-in campaign, undated (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Gus Gus, undated (Box 52, Folder 1)
- GW student arrested in gun running scheme Matthew Strong, 1992 June (Box 15, Folder 11)
- GW University gay dance marred by hecklers, 1995 November 27 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Hard copies, 1980-1982 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  This appears to be a list of gay related stories in papers including the Blade and other newspapers.
- Hard copies, 1981-1983 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Hard copies, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Hard copies, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Hard copies, 1985 [1/2], 1985 January - May (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Hard copies, 1985 [2/2], 1985 June - December (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Hard copies, 1986 [1/2], 1986 January - June (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Hard copies, 1986 [2/2], 1986 July - December (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Hard copies, 1987 [1/2], 1987 January - June (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Hard copies, 1987 [2/2], 1987 July-December (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Hard copies [1/2], 1988 January - June (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Hard copies [2/2], 1988 July - December (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Hard copies [1/4], 1989 January - April (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Hard copies [2/4], 1989 May - July (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Hard copies [3/4], 1989 August - November (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Hard copies [4/4], 1989 December, 1992 September (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Hard copies [1/4], 1990 January - March (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Hard copies [2/4], 1990 April - June (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Hard copies [3/4], 1990 July - September (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Hard copies [4/4], 1990 October - December (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Hard copies [1/4], 1991 January - March (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Hard copies [2/4], 1991 April - June (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Hard copies [3/4], 1991 July - September (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Hard copies [4/4], 1991 October - December (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Hassell v. Warring and Kinnaham, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Hatch, undated (Box 58, Folder 4)
- Hate Crime, undated (Box 65, Folder 11)
- Hate Crimes Prevention Act of 1997 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Hate Crimes report, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- HC PA, undated (Box 68, Folder 9)
- HC' TV Labels, undated (Box 60, Folder 10)
- Health, undated (Box 59, Folder 4)
- Heaven's Gate Cult "Gay" Angle, undated (Box 70, Folder 9)
- Helms bill/Gay civil rights in Federal work force, 1997 January (Box 48, Folder 14)
- Henry Foster nominated for US Surgeon General, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Hickham AFB witch hunt probe A.F. Inspector General's report, undated (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Hill hearing set for gays in schools [1/3], undated (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Hill hearing set for gays in schools [2/3], undated (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Hill hearing set for gays in schools [3/3], undated (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Hill staffer wins AIDS discrimination suit, 1995 August (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Hill Update Issue, 1997 May 23 (Box 55, Folder 15)
- HIV, AIDS and the Law by Mark S. Senak, MD, 1996 June (Box 11, Folder 8)
- HIV Prevention Act - Rep. Coburn, 1997 March 13 (Box 55, Folder 13)
- House ethics panel invites partner to register, 1995 December (Box 46, Folder 10)
- House members call for an ENDA hearing, 1996 February (Box 43, Folder 15)
- House passes DOMA, 1996 July 12 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- House Race, 2000 (Box 68, Folder 12)
- House-Senate probe of DNC-White House fundraising, undated (Box 41, Folder 18)
- HRC Dinner, 1995 November 11 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- HRC Hill "Ratings" 104th Congress, undated (Box 57, Folder 6)
- HRC Voting Guides, undated (Box 54, Folder 25)
- HRCF changes name, 1995 October (Box 8, Folder 3)
- HRCF lobbies Clinton for endorsement, 1995 August (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Human Remains Act - DC Law 11-129, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Hustler robs john, undated (Box 43, Folder 3)
- IBM, undated (Box 53, Folder 28)
- ICC members March on DC, 1991 August 04 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- ICCAN Burglary, undated (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Idaho bombing, undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
- ILGA - Helms Amendment, 1994 January 26 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Immigration bill bars HIV treatment, 1996 September 25 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- In the Life, undated (Box 68, Folder 3)
- Inaugural box, undated (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Inaugural credentials, undated (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Inaugural events, undated (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Index, 1969-1979 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Index, 1969-1979 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Inner Light, undated (Box 66, Folder 1)
- INS asks State Dept to conduct gay persecution check, 1995 September (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Inspector Gadget Press Packet, undated (Box 66, Folder 10)
- Internet Uber Alles, undated (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Internet, undated (Box 54, Folder 1)
- Investigative techniques seminar, 1986 February 05 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Israeli Parliament member issues "death sentence" to gays, 1996 January (Box 47, Folder 18)
- Issues, delegates - Democratic Convention, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- It's Elementary, undated (Box 59, Folder 16)
- J & D Memorial Foundation - Spencer, West Virginia, undated (Box 27, Folder 23)
- Jack Keegal assault ("pick-up" at Fireplace), 1996 November 03 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Jacob Orozco, 1980-1997 (Box 52, Folder 10)
- Jeff Stryker interview, 1997 March 15 (Box 49, Folder 16)
- Jenny Jones Murder, 1995 March 09 - 1996 December 05 (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Jerry Brown and Ribavirin flap, undated (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Jerry Smith, undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Jesse Jackson's statehood primer, undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Jews, undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Jim Elliott murder, 1992 April 14 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Jim Graham City Council race, 1998 March 09 (Box 71, Folder 1)
- Jim Kolbe, undated (Box 68, Folder 8)
- Jim Patterson - USDA official, undated (Box 41, Folder 13)
- Job bias bill, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- John Hill ADW case, 1995 October (Box 46, Folder 3)
- John McCain (Campaign Info), undated (Box 58, Folder 9)
- John Vitullo, undated (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Joint assignments, n.d., undated (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Josh Lipsman, undated (Box 54, Folder 2)
- JRs Outdoor Cafe application, 1995 June (Box 8, Folder 21)
- JRs flap over outdoor caf, 1995 September (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Justen Bennett-MacCubbin- name change discrimation lawsuit, 1996 July 01 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Justice Dept. directive threaten Globe groups, 1994 December (Box 69, Folder 5)
- Justin Elzie USMC, undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Kameny - NGLTF letter exchange, 1995 November (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Kameny for Congress anniversary, undated (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Keith Boykin Meets Leaders of Zimbabwe, 1997 July (Box 55, Folder 12)
- Kinkos caper, 1996 April 11 (Box 43, Folder 13)
- Kristina Campbell files: 1992 AIDSWalk - Washington (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Kristina Campbell files: 1992 Elections info (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Kristina Campbell files: AIDS Info, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Kristina Campbell files: Audre Lorde, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files Cancer, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files Clinton Administration Appointments, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files Colleges/Universities, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files Colorado, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Kristina Campbell files: correspondence, undated (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Kristina Campbell files: Dignity/Washington - 20th Anniversary, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Kristina Campbell files: Fairfax School Board, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Kristina Campbell files: Genetics and homosexuality, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Kristina Campbell files: Hate crimes/gay bashing, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Kristina Campbell files: Lesbian health interviews and contacts, 1993 April (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Kristina Campbell files: Local/statewide Rights Laws (various), undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Kristina Campbell files: loose papers, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Kristina Campbell files: loose papers, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Kristina Campbell files: loose papers, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Kristina Campbell files: loose papers, 1995-1996 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Kristina Campbell files: loose papers, 1995-1996 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Kristina Campbell files: loose papers, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Kristina Campbell files: loose papers, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Kristina Campbell files: loose papers, 1995 July 14 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Kristina Campbell files: loose papers, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Kristina Campbell files: loose papers pick-up for Lisa Keen, n.d., undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Kristina Campbell files: Marijuana legalization, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Kristina Campbell files: Maryland - other, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Kristina Campbell files: Maryland - State Rights Bill, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files Military, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Kristina Campbell files: Minnesota, undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Kristina Campbell files: Murders/bashings, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Kristina Campbell files: National Endowment for the Arts, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Kristina Campbell files: NIH Reauth - House, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Kristina Campbell files: Occasions, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files Passages conference, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Kristina Campbell files: Press Kit Creating Change Conference, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files Pride of Washington, Inc., undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Kristina Campbell files: Queer Nation - various, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files Religion, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files Republicans, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Kristina Campbell files: St. Patrick's Day Parade - NYC, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Kristina Campbell files: Take Back the Night, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Kristina Campbell files: Youth services and school board, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1995 March 31 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1995 April 14 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1994 September 02 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1994 September 09 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1994 September 16 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1994 October 14 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1994 October 21 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1994 October 28 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1994 January 07 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1994 January 14 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1994 January 21 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1994 February 01 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1994 February 04 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1994 February 11 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1994 February 18 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1994 February 25 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1994 March 04 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1994 March 11 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1994 March 18 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1994 March 25 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1994 April 01 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1994 April 08 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1994 April 15 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1994 April 22 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1994 April 29 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1994 May 06 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1994 May 13 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1994 May 20 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1994 May 27 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1993 September 03 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1993 September 10 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1993 September 17 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1993 September 24 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1993 October 01 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1993 October 08 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1993 October 15 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1993 October 22 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1993 October 29 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1993 November 05 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1993 November 12 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1993 November 19 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1993 November 26 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1993 December 03 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1993 December 10 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1993 December 17 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files, 1993 December 24 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Kristina Campbell reporter's notebooks 1-3, 1992 September 21 - December 28 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  Notebooks include the following topics: 1: Act-Up marajana protest, Lesbian/breast cancer -suzanne hayes, 1992 skills building conference AIDS amp; black church, Act-up NY protest ashes on the lawn Notebook 2: Maunter project Tuesday night out double jeopardy, GWA coffee house feature, Pride of Washington meetings, DC Coalition, World Aids day, We are Everywhere Ruth F. Notebook 3: Congressional waring Rs on Gs in military, Audre Lorde tribute, republican majority coalition, historcal association: gender, sexuality in native amp; latin americans, lesbian culture in 20th century
- Kristina Campbell reporter's notebooks 4-6, 1993 January 5 - March 24 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  Notebooks include the following topics: #4: Act-up meeting, WWC suburan MD clinic dedication, Rosales Murder-Shelly perry, Triangle ball, Pride of Washington meeting, GLB returned Peace Corp mgt, Md senate hearing sexual orientation bill, notebook #5 interview w/ Crae Pridgen et al, interview w/Jan Nyquist, Rosales vigil, Enlace mtg, Arlington GL mtg, Pride of Washington mtg, Alexandria GLCA mtg. notebook #6 Gay people of Laurel mtg, notes from NGLTF's hate crime video, Fairfax library board hearing, Brian Scott md update, library meeting
- Kristina Campbell reporter's noteboks 7-9, 1993 March 24 - June 16 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  Notebooks include the following topics: # 7, Fairfax library board cont., Amelie Zurn lesbian health care, Keen-Blade lesbian health coverage, Mautner project mtg, Fairfax anti-Blade protest, Notebook #8 Lesbian health briefings--press conference, lesbians of color cultural event, bisexual conf. workshop, Lesbian avengers march, march on washington and gays on the street interviews, lesbian wellness project mtg, notebook #9 Fairfax co. library board mtg, Black Lesbian and Gay Pride Day planning mtg, Lesbian wellness project mtg, mautner project mtg, Angela Pattatucci/ NIH lesbian research, Fairfax library bd. budget hearing
- Kristina Campbell reporter's notebooks 10-12, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  Notebooks include the following topics: #10 DC Pride parade, Asians Town Forum, Closing Plenary of NLGHF conf. Lesbian Avengers mtg, Candidates forum council chair, Notebook #11 G/L Health conference, notebook #12 David North, Fleming appointment anouncement etc.
- Kristina Campbell reporter's notebooks 13-15, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  Notebooks include the following topics: #13 Pride of Washington bd. Mtg, lesbian avengers mtg, Actu-up washington mtg, Christian Coalition speakers/conv. Mautner board mtg, fairfax co. board of supervisors, Blade theft arrest/trial in mont. Co. Notebook 14 Nova gays coalition re: blade, Jessie Oakes manassas lesbian custody battle, FC library board regular mtg, Breast cancer rally, prince william tp council candidate, library bd. policy committee notebook 15 creating change
- Kristina Campbell reporter's noteboks 16-18, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  Notebooks include the following topics: #16 Nat'l coalition on youth and sexual orientation, GLIC mtg, mautner mtg, Jennifer Thompson/ Hung Jury arrest, pride mtg. Notebook 17 stonewall 25 DC org committee Notebook 18 GLOV mtg, Queer nation, GLIC, Mont. Co. council comt discusses gay book, clinton budget shalala and Gebbie press confs, gay adoption seminar
- Kristina Campbell reporter's notebooks 19-21, 1994 March 1 - May 11 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  Notebooks include the following topics: #19 Hanna repeal hearing, Roberta Achtenberg, Pride of Washington mtg. Notebook #20 WWC lesbians and aging day, GLIC mtg, Women's history month program, Mary Plumb on stark bill, Notebook #21 Lesbian health training at G'town U, Ffax co. library board mtg, Faith forum
- Kristina Campbell reporter's notebooks 22-24, 1994 March 13 - June 07 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  Notebooks include the following topics: #22 APA women's health conf, NCRL reception and panel, detective shelton on sam swift murder, lesbian health advocacy network mtg Notebook #23 Day in the life of Gebbie, Amelie Zurn goodbye party Notebook #24 Amelie Zurn goodbye interview, Stein Club mayoral endorsemetn mtg
- Kristina Campbell reporter's notebooks 25-27, 1994 June 22 - September 22 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  Notebooks include the following topics: #25 ILGA conference/ NAMBLA vote, Arlington G/L Assn. mtg, Notebook #26Latino forum, POC/ENDA press conf, ENDA hearing, Notebook #27 Mautner board, Ffax board of supervisors, maryland appeals court north v north, ffax count library bd
- Kristina Campbell reporter's notebooks, n.d., undated (Box 35, Folder 2)
  Notebooks include the following topics: notebook 1 CARe ACT, ENDA, words out notebook 2 Susan Hester, mautner board, notebook 3 breast health workshop
- Kristina Campbell reporter's notebooks, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  Notebooks include the following topics: notebook 1 HRCF legislative briefing, mautner project (2/9/ 1995) GLAA mtg (2/14/95) notebook 2 EALHAN FDA, Mautner, ADASA interviews 1/19/1995 notebook 3 GLCSC
- Kristina Campbell reporter's notebooks, 1994-1995 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  Notebooks include the following topics: notebook 1 Achtenberg resignation, mautner (4/13/95), notebook 2 Barney Frank - pflag, B. Frank cong. Outlook, gerry studds cong. Outlook, LHAN mtg, Mautner mtg, Alexandria GLCA mtg (11/20/94 -1/3/1995) notebook 3 Anti-discrimination hearing 2/16/1995, mautner 2/23/1995
- Kristina Campbell reporter's notebooks, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Kristina Campbell reporter's notebooks, undated (Box 36, Folder 2)
- LaCage Aux Follies - liquor license suspension, undated (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Larry Frankel C and P flap, 1984 October (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Larry Kramer flap, 1993 April 25 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Latino youths attack gay couple - gay bashing, 1995 October 29 (Box 47, Folder 20)
- LBJ Grove assault by Park Police sargent, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Leather Weekend, undated (Box 66, Folder 3)
- Lefante, Schott Appointed to D.C. Rights Commission, undated (Box 55, Folder 10)
- Lesbian Dale McCormick runs for Congress in Maine, 1995 August (Box 44, Folder 1)
- [The Lesbian and Gay Immigration Rights Task Force, briefing kit], 2000 (Box 60, Folder 15)
- Lesbian health misc, undated (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Lesbian threatened, stalked by man walking dog in Woodley Park, 1995 July 11 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Levi Straus Co., undated (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Library of Congress bans sexual orientation discrimination Gay Fed Workers, 1994 February 28 (Box 69, Folder 2)
- Living benefits firms insurance, undated (Box 47, Folder 10)
- Liz Lerman Dance Exchange, undated (Box 52, Folder 7)
- Local government officials, undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Log Cabin, undated (Box 58, Folder 10)
- London trip, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 1)